Sabrina Ferguson

6578 Brynhurst Dr Tucker, GA 30084 770.634.7003 | skheath@gatech.edu

Georgia Tech graduate with a degree in Computational Media and a focus on User Interface and User Interaction design. Experience in a wide range of industries and company sizes utilizing various skills and tools to complete projects. Personal focus and passion in front end web development with interest in strengthening skills in server-side development.

Experience

m2M Strategies

UX Engineer

April 2014 - November 2014

(GetOne Rewards startup company merged with m2M Strategies) Responsible for designing interfaces for franchise marketing administration. Focus on user experience and improving the usability of existing systems. Planned out use cases, mocked up wireframes with Balsamiq and developing the pages with HTML/CSS and Javascript. Worked in Java and .NET environments.

GetOne Rewards

UX Engineer

February 2014 - April 2014

Worked in a dev environment to mock up and design prototypes using Balsamiq, Photoshop and HTML/CSS with Javascript. Redesigned the iPad Kiosk app to improve the user experience and ease the process of checkout. Maintained and wrote up documents of interaction and requirements for the development team.

PlayOn Sports

Web Developer

August 2011 - February 2014

Developed and improved front end user interfaces for PlayOn Sports online services. Worked mainly with HTML, CSS and Javascript while furthering skills in Ruby on Rails. Designed wireframes and mockups for development and presentations, ensured W3C compliant HTML and clean CSS. Programmed features for the PlayOn website in Ruby on Rails.

Allconnect

Web Developer & Designer

March 2011 - August 2011

Designed prototypes for presentations on new products. Worked on front end design and improved user interaction in products. Designed graphics for web as well as print media.

Hiring For Hope Volunteer Web Developer\Graphic Designer

August 2009 - Present

Designed, developed and maintain the online presence for a 501c3 public charity life management community. Overall responsibility is to maintain and update website content and graphics, design new and creative images and branding concepts for all programs and initiatives. Ensure website is accessible and optimized for search engines.

Education

Georgia Institute of Technology

2006-2010

Computational Media Bachelor of Science

Links

http://sabrinaferguson.com http://lnkd.in/B6F5yr

Technical Skills Summary

HTML CSS (LESS/SASS) Javascript (JQuery) Ruby on Rails PHP MySQL Java

UI Design ASP .NET

SEO

Software

Balsamiq Eclipse IDE

Adobe Suite

Photoshop

Dreamweaver

Flash

InDesign

Illustrator

Microsoft Office

Word

Excel

Access